Pair of jokers.
What are you doing?
Hello, aunties.
Ranran.
You have a guest.
I brought your favorite roses.
And soup.
Who's a guest?
Zhuang Qiang.
Don't you understand what I'm saying?
Take your stuff and get the hell out.
Ranran.
Try my stewed pork trotters.
They're delicious.
They smell so good.
Here.
Ranran.
Have a taste.
They melt in your mouth.
If they melt in your mouth,
why don't you get lost?
I made them just for you.
Stewed them for over three hours.
Try them.
The doctor ordered
a light diet after surgery.
No greasy food.
Ranran.
Mine is
rich in protein,
and good for recovery.
It's delicious.
Come on.
Try some.
Sister Lan, which one do you prefer?
If you ask me, Little Chen is better.
That other kid isn't much to look at.
And he seems a bit dumb.
Yours is burnt, isn't it?
Here, Yiran.
Eat mine.
Ranran.
This is too plain.
And it's overcooked.
Leave it if you can't finish.
Small, frequent meals are good for the stomach.
You should go back first.
I have some family matters to deal with.
Such a good show,
I have to keep watching.
Zhang Lijuan.
Then I'll watch it next time.
I'm going to buy a fish head for soup.
Ranran.
You used to
love my stewed pork trotters the most.
That was before.
I don't like them anymore.
Who are you?
Can't you tell what my relationship with her is?
We were together for so many years.
Who the hell are you?
Then can't you see
what her body language says right now?
Ranran.
Who are you?
He asked who you are.
Me.
I'm Li Yiran's mom.
Auntie!
Want some pork trotters?
They melt in your mouth.
Too greasy.
Hold this.
This tie is quite nice.
Yeah.
Imported from Italy.
Pretty expensive.
Come on, step outside for a bit.
Auntie.
Don't shout. Don't shout.
Auntie!
Ow, ow, ow!
You're coming with me!
How about
having some soup?
Throw that away.
This...
You had chopsticks.
But you didn't give them to me earlier.
They're his.
Then I won't use them.
You want to eat it?
My cooking is pretty good, right?
You made this?
I made it.
Are you hungry?
I made you some fish soup.
Who was it that said earlier
I couldn't eat meat or fish?
Well, that depends
on who made it.
Where's Wu Huilian?
She was at the hospital for three days,
so I told her to go home and rest.
I'll just leave it here
to let it cool.
By the way,
that tattooed guy from the other day
was caught by the police.
He confessed to all his crimes.
The police followed the leads
and caught the other suspects.
Now we just wait for the trial.
That's great.
Xizi's spirit in heaven
can finally rest in peace.
You should go home and rest too.
Look how tired you are.
Don't worry, I can manage by myself.
No way.
I have to stay with you.
Alright.
Just pour me a little bit.
It'll cool faster.
Welcome home!
Welcome, welcome!
Oh my gosh!
Welcome home! Welcome home!
Okay, okay, okay.
You scared me to death!
I thought something had happened.
Everything's fine.
Let's welcome our heroine home from the hospital!
Thanks, Yangyang.
Yiran!
Auntie Juan!
I'm just glad you're okay. You're finally back.
Heroine! Heroine!
Ranran!
What's the meaning of this?
Ranran.
Can I have a breakup dinner with you?
Is that okay?
Let's part on good terms.
Come on.
Let's go, let's go.
We're leaving, let's go, let's go.
Go ahead.
What else do you have to say?
Get it all out right now.
We said this is a breakup dinner.
Why are you still being so serious?
I know.
You're someone who hates dragging things out.
I shouldn't say anything to try and make you stay.
Today, I just want to tell you...
We both came from small towns.
Shanghai is just too big.
It's so easy to lose your way.
If I had nothing to lean on,
I really couldn't stay.
If you're still making excuses even now,
there's really no need.
Oh, by the way.
Your mom came to see me.
Wu Huilian.
What did she want with you?
It was right here.
She dragged me over here.
Sorry about earlier.
I was a little rude.
It's fine, Auntie.
Actually, I
was also very impolite.
Did Yiran ever tell you about her family?
Not really.
She just said her dad passed away.
What about her mom?
I didn't dare ask.
She'd get mad whenever I asked.
Alright then.
Let me tell you about it.
Eight years ago,
right in this very spot,
her Pops and I ran a food stall.
One night,
some thugs were bullying a little girl.
I couldn't just stand by and watch,
so I started fighting them,
and almost got myself killed.
Just when I was in serious danger,
her Pops came back from delivering takeout.
Her Pops came over to help me.
But the thugs, using their numbers,
beat her Pops half to death.
In a moment of impulse,
I grabbed a nearby knife,
and rushed at their leader.
With just a few strikes,
that man was dead.
I spent eight years on the inside.
And Yiran spent eight years on the outside.
For these eight years,
she hasn't had a single family member by her side.
You are her first love,
and once the person she trusted most.
I know all about what happened between you two.
What you want,
Yiran can't give you.
And what she wants,
you can't give her either.
As for me,
I only want one thing.
I want her to be happy.
Zhuang.
Yiran is my entire world.
If anyone tries to bully her,
I'm not afraid of going back inside again.
The thing between you two is over now.
Let her go,
and you'll be freeing yourself, too.
With this drink,
Auntie toasts you.
Here.
Yiran,
even though we can't be together anymore,
can we still be friends?
We're both adults now.
There's no need to be so sentimental.
May our paths
never cross again.
Why are you back?
I...
I didn't even cook for you.
I grabbed a bowl of rice noodles on the street.
I'm not hungry.
Ran... uh... ate...
I ate too much.
Went for a run to digest it.
I'm a little thirsty.
Let's go.
I'll make you tea when we get back. Let's go.
You just got out of the hospital and you went running?
You're gonna shake your head until you pass out.
Hello, Mr. Wang.
About what we discussed, you really can't offer a discount?
We've worked together for so long.
Please do me a favor.
Mr. Zhou,
I really had no choice last time.
I'll lose money if I lower the price.
Then can we meet and talk?
To see exactly where
we can further cut costs.
What are you doing?
Xiao... Xiaofang.
Do you think our water is free?
Why are you back?
Can't I come back to my own home?
Let me wash these.
You've been working hard all day.
Go get some rest.
Go on.
How are things on your end?
The unit cost overrun isn't much,
but the volume is huge this time.
Running the total, it's 30% over budget!
Don't we still have cash in the company account?
My dear young Master Zhou,
Do you know how much the company's monthly rent, utilities,
payroll, and social security cost in total?
We're already operating at a loss.
Now with Mr. Wang raising his prices...
Why did he suddenly raise his prices?
Boss, you're using all high-end custom models.
Mr. Wang absolutely won't lower his prices.
I put all our cash flow into the products
just to maintain our reputation.
Who knew he'd pull a stunt like this?
Business is all about profit.
There's no room for sentiment.
We either cut the service quality...
I'm not cutting the quality.
Besides, cutting the quality is useless.
If the clients aren't satisfied,
our reputation takes a hit,
and all our hard work goes down the drain.
Then how about...
we ask Mr. Zhou Senior for help?
Even if I have to tough it out alone,
I'll never ask him for help.
Isn't she lovely?
She is.
Beautiful, right?
Beautiful.
Her name is Li Yiran.
She's my daughter.
She graduated from a top university in Shanghai.
Such class.
People who've lived in the big city are just different.
She even worked for a Fortune 500 company.
A Fortune 500 company?
Wouldn't she have hundreds of people under her?
Do you want to exhaust her?
Managing that many people!
Though she did manage a small team.
Now, for my sake,
she came back to this little town.
That head of hers
is incredibly sharp.
She inherited all my good genes.
Then her boyfriend must be pretty amazing too, right?
What's wrong with you?
Always rubbing salt in my wounds!
She has high standards.
She hasn't found anyone she likes yet.
Should we set her up with someone?
She's seen the big wide world.
How could she settle for someone from our little town?
No way.
What do you guys mean?
Gathering intel in a town this small!
The company is going bankrupt!
When did you get back?
Zoning out?
You said before
that I was a whatchamacallit...
Whatever industry I join, it goes under.
What was it?
What kind of jinx?
Industry jinx.
Right.
It really is
so damn frustrating.
Before, I
went to an escape room
to work as an NPC.
I moved bricks,
and carried frozen pork.
I did a bunch of random jobs.
And they all went out of business.
Even when I went to sell fish,
I only did it for a bit,
and the next day, the boss stopped selling fish
and switched to selling yarn.
Selling yarn?
No.
Actually, let me tell you,
I really like working at Joy Bells.
Being there...
I'm actually pretty happy.
You're saying all this...
Did something happen to Joy Bells?
The ship of Joy Bells
has crashed into me, the industry jinx.
I'm afraid it's really going to sink.
Don't overthink it right now.
I think,
even if Joy Bells goes under...
Bite your tongue!
You jinx, knock on wood three times!
You're that superstitious?
Then I'll go get that fraud from before
to light a candle in the southeast corner for you.
If I ever believe that fraud again,
I'll eat shit.
Actually, I don't think you need to be so anxious.
Think about it.
You've already made a name for yourself
as a top matchmaker.
Whichever matchmaking agency you go to,
wouldn't they all want you?
It's mainly that right now,
I can't bear to leave Boss Zhou
and Wumei's gang.
At first, I sort of
couldn't stand them.
Who knew that as we spent time together,
I'd get so attached to them, you know?
They are pretty good people.
This is so damn annoying!
What are you doing?
Zhou Fang isn't back.
Who asked about him?
You're still pretending with me?
Are you going to let me read or what?
Bro.
Did something happen to Joy Bells?
Zhou Fang didn't tell you?
You've got some nerve, Zhou Fang.
I thought you'd already cut ties with your dad.
I didn't expect you to give up at the first sign of trouble.
And to think I actually wanted to help you.
I'm such an idiot.
Wumei.
Get in touch with Mr. He again tomorrow.
Mr. He? I'm afraid our chances are slim.
Dad.
Mr. Zhou, what brings you here?
I heard you can't even pay your suppliers.
I thought it was a joke.
But it turns out it's true.
Honest to God.
I really didn't say anything this time.
I came here on my own.
Don't blame him.
Go make some tea.
Okay, Mr. Zhou.
Dad.
If you came all the way here just to mock me...
Can't you talk to your dad nicely?
At the end of the day,
the initial funding for Joy Bells
came from me.
So the fact that I haven't bankrupted Joy Bells yet,
must be really disappointing to you.
Do you think with your abilities,
you can still hold on?
The ship is falling apart,
yet you insist on setting sail.
It's my ship,
and I'll make sure it sails.
The problem is you don't even have fuel.
How are you going to sail?
Zhou Fang.
Look at the state you're in.
What can you give Chen Xiaofang?
She loves money more than anything.
Would she board your sinking ship?
Dad.
Do you really understand love?
You're just a businessman.
A businessman who only cares about money.
If you understood love even a little bit,
would our relationship be like this now?
My relationship with Xiaofang is none of your business.
And I will keep Joy Bells running smoothly.
When you can't even afford to eat,
love doesn't mean shit.
I'm done talking to you.
When you figure things out,
come back to me.
Mr. Zhou,
leaving so soon?
The tea is just ready.
I'll pass.
I'm sorry. Give me some time.
Once I build a future you can rely on,
I'll come back to you.
Chen Xiaofang.
Mr. Zhou.
You're a businessman.
You should at least keep your word.
You took my money,
so you should do as you promised.
What do you mean?
Because of you, Zhou Fang
has completely fallen out
with me, his own father.
Mr. Zhou,
as for your money,
I haven't touched a single cent.
What do you mean?
When you gave me that one million,
you put a price tag on my marriage to your son.
But now,
I don't think one million is enough.
No amount you give me would be enough.
Because I love him.
All this time,
Zhou Fang has followed your orders
to be a good, obedient son.
But have you ever considered what he really wants?
Now, he makes his own decisions.
He takes responsibility for his employees.
And he takes care of his family.
Can't you see
how much he's grown?
Please wait, Mr. Zhou.
This card...
I think when the day comes
that Zhou Fang truly makes you proud,
you can use it as your blessing
and give it back to me.
Damn it!
Zhou Fang, you son of a bitch!
Teaming up with your Pops to piss me off!
Old Wu
Why are you here?
Have you eaten yet?
I brought you some food.
I haven't eaten yet.
Food is fuel, you know.
How can you go without eating?
That's very thoughtful, Old Wu.
I know the company has had some issues lately.
But don't worry.
I will always stand by you.
Sister Lan.
It's a shame you don't open a restaurant with your skills.
Just eat your food.
And stop talking nonsense.
Boss Zhou.
There's a favor I'd like to ask you.
Yiran's birthday is coming up in a few days.
As you know,
I haven't celebrated her birthday for years.
I originally wanted to book
the restaurant where Xiaofu held his banquet.
But it's too hard to book.
Okay, I'll call and book it for you now.
Thank you. Thanks a lot.
Leave some for others.
Your mouth
is only good for talking nonsense and eating.
It's just so delicious!
Just one last piece.
Old Wu.
I've made the call for you.
It's booked. I got you the biggest private room.
Thanks, Boss Zhou.
Zhou Fang, get the hell out here!
Xiaofang.
Zhou Fang!
You, get over to me!
Xiao...
Why are you here, Xiaofang?
Zhou Fang,
did you think by blocking me,
your business would succeed?
Did you think by not contacting me,
you're being responsible?
If I were really after your money,
I would've stopped contacting you.
I would've stopped contacting you long ago!
Xiaofang,
that's not what I meant.
You misunderstood me.
Give me a break.
Chen Xiaofang.
You misunderstood me.
I really didn't mean that.
Do you know what the most important thing is
when two people are together?
It's trust.
I know you want to do big things
and succeed on your own,
but have you ever considered my feelings?
The future, the future...
It's only a future if we support each other.
What is it when you're alone?
Then why don't you just live alone?
Xiaofang,
I'm... I'm sorry.
I can give up everything in this world,
except you.
I don't care about anything else, except you.
I was wrong.
Still trying to jump?
You still can't reach even if you jump.
You're tall.
Tall or not, you still don't get to kiss me.
Let's go.
What are you doing in broad daylight?
What are you doing?
Nothing, nothing.
Xiaofang! Xiaofang!
What made you want to get your hair done today?
Isn't it Yiran's birthday?
Give me a style that's not too flashy,
but not too ordinary either.
Just make it fit a mother's vibe.
You know that kind of hairstyle.
You don't need to tell me that.
Don't you trust my skills?
You'll get a massive eye roll from me.
Did you forget
what you made me look like last time?
Zhang Lijuan!
You permed it for me,
saying it was the Marilyn Monroe look!
Sister Lan,
the curling iron broke.
So it's just me doing your hair today.
Good that it's broken.
Time really flies.
The kids grew up in the blink of an eye.
I still remember the first time Yiran got a haircut here.
She wanted a bob cut.
Her long hair,
gone with just one snip.
She cried so hard.
I comforted her for half an hour, but it was no use.
She's loved looking pretty since she was little.
By the way,
I have a secret to tell you.
What is it?
I want to give Yiran a surprise.
What kind of surprise?
Hello, Xiaoli.
Yes, yes, exactly.
My daughter is a very picky eater.
If you don't prepare it carefully,
she won't eat anything at all.
Right, right.
Thanks for your help.
Make sure it's perfect.
Otherwise she really won't eat.
Okay.
Wu Huilian.
Are you kidding me?
I'm not the Queen.
Why make me sound so high-maintenance?
Do you know how hard it is to book this restaurant?
I even had our Boss Zhou book it for me.
It cost so much money, so it has to be perfect.
Right?
We have to do this in style.
You're really something.
You sure know how to handle people.
Come here.
Mom made these especially for you.
Longevity noodles.
It smells so good.
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
Come on.
Why are you just standing there?
Hurry up.
Sit.
Thanks.
What are you thanking me for?
No need to be so polite with your mom.
Hurry up, try it.
Mix it up. Mix it up.
Wait a minute.
Birthday gift.
Thank you.
Why are you saying thank you again?
Sweetie,
could you please
promise Mom one thing?
What?
Just promise me first, okay?
Fine.
This is the birthday outfit Mom carefully prepared for you.
Once you put it on,
you'll definitely blind everyone with your beauty.
So pretty.
You look just like a star from Hong Kong, China!
Beautiful!
I shouldn't have listened to you.
What is this?
Talk about blinding everyone...
you've completely blinded me!
It's so pretty, how does it blind you?
It looks absolutely gorgeous!
It really does look good.
But there was no need to go this far.
What do I look like standing here?
Like a monkey in a show.
I'm not standing here anymore.
You stand here if you want.
It's just a birthday,
not a wedding.
Come back, come back!
Sweetie,
you'll have to get married eventually anyway.
Just treat this as a rehearsal.
You look so pretty.
Then I'm not wearing this.
Hold it, hold it.
Yiran!
You coming here is enough,
why did you bring a gift?
Oh my god!
You're dressed like a movie star today!
Absolutely beautiful!
Thanks to Auntie Juan for doing my hair.
Yiran,
may your grace bloom like orchids,
and flourish year after year.
Happy birthday!
Thank you, Brother Amin.
What Brother Amin?
It's Uncle Amin.
You're messing up the generations.
Thank you, Uncle Amin.
Yangyang is dressed so cutely today.
Don't hit Yiran.
Go on in, go on in.
Come on, Yangyang.
Go inside.
Come on.
Isn't Sister Yiran pretty?
Pretty.
Yiran.
Happy birthday.
Uncle Chen!
Thank you.
Take your time, take your time.
Great, great.
Does it look weird?
Not at all.
It looks great, really great.
Brother Chen!
Welcome, welcome!
Hello, hello!
Happy birthday!
Step forward to hand over the gift!
This is so frustrating.
If he'd just taken a few more steps,
our families would be celebrating a double joy.
Wu Huilian!
Am I wrong?
Slow down, slow down.
So, about this gift...
You actually bought a gift?
Yeah, it's your birthday.
Then help me carry it inside.
Sure.
Beautiful.
Xiaofang.
How are you so pretty?
Thank you.
Here, happy birthday.
Thanks.
Help me take it inside.
Sure, sure.
Thank you.
I know you like practical things.
Remember to accept the transfer.
Boss Chen is so generous.
Go inside and take a seat.
Let's go, let's go.
What did you just say?
We got the project.
Really?
Yeah.
You're here.
Old Wu.
Go inside and sit down, hurry.
Alright.
The room looks great.
Why isn't Uncle Daren here yet?
Did you tell him what time to come?
Of course I did.
Sorry, sorry.
Uncle Daren.
I'm late.
Happy birthday, Yiran.
Thanks, Uncle Daren.
You're all sweaty.
You're right on time.
Let's go.
Sorry.
I'm late.
Not at all.
Go inside and have some water.
Okay, sure.
Yiran.
Why are you spacing out? Hurry up.
You look so pretty today.
Happy birthday to you
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you.
It's too early for that.
I have another surprise for you.
Juanzi,
bring it here.
Auntie Huilian,
is this a family heirloom or what?
Pretty much.
Here.
Hold out both hands.
I sold the old house,
added some money,
and paid a down payment.
Don't worry about the mortgage from now on.
I'll pay it.
You have a new house now.
What did you say?
Who told you to sell the house?
I... I... I...
We...
We've lived in that old house for decades.
I just thought we should get a new one.
You'll get married eventually anyway,
so consider it a dowry from Mom.
Why would you do something this big
without even discussing it with me?
It's not just a house.
That's the home Pops left for me.
As long as I live there, I feel like Pops is still here.
What gave you the right to just sell it?
Yiran.
Don't get upset. Take it easy.
Your mom means well.
Exactly, Yiran.
It wasn't easy for your mom to save up all those years.
Isn't this for your own good?
If you don't like it,
I'll go and return it.
Wu Huilian,
you have no idea what I like
or what I'm afraid of.
You don't know what I want.
I... I just thought
we'd lived in that house for so many years.
I didn't want you to be trapped in there forever.
Right?
We always have to look forward in life.
Come on.
Yeah, yeah.
Come on, come on.
Let's have a drink.
It's a birthday.
Right.
Wu Huilian.
From the very beginning, the one trapping me is you.
It's you!
Yiran.
Yiran!
Auntie Lan, I'll go talk to her.
It's fine, it's fine.
Have a seat. Have a seat.
Don't take it to heart.
That child, Yiran...
She just has a stubborn temper.
About what happened today,
you were indeed in the wrong.
Pops...
Brother Chen, Brother Chen...
It's my fault.
I really...
just don't know what she actually likes.
Yiran.
Yiran!
Yiran, you... just calm down.
I can't calm down!
We can talk about this properly.
There was no need to embarrass Auntie Lan in front of so many people.
Fine.
I was wrong.
It's my fault.
It's all my fault, okay?
I... I didn't...
I... I didn't mean it that way.
I didn't mean it that way.
I just wanted to tell you that
once some words are spoken,
they... they can't be taken back.
Do you understand?
But she didn't even discuss it with me.
She just sold my home.
Sold my memories.
Sold the only keepsake Pops left me.
What gives her the right?
Did she even consider my feelings?
Yes, Auntie Lan didn't think this through.
But those things you said just now, you...
you really crossed the line.
Why are you defending her, too?
You've never watched your Pops die right in front of you.
Or been bullied and laughed at.
Let alone having a mom who killed someone and went to jail.
So,
what gives you the right to lecture me now?
Yiran! Yiran!
Yiran
This house,
if you don't want to sell it,
we don't have to.
I'll go find the buyer tomorrow
and just return his deposit.
At worst, we just lose some money.
I can cancel the new house too.
Please don't be mad anymore, okay?
Mom was wrong.
Who is it?
Sister Lan.
It's me.
Hongyu